splitly.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Splitly

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Splitly.com

**BY VISITING  **Splitly.com **, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.**

**OVERVIEW**

SPLITLY LLC (“Company”) is committed to protecting your privacy online.  This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect through this website at [Splitly.com](http://splitly.com/) (the “Site” or “Website”).

Visitors and any users of the Site are referred to as “user”, “you” and “your” and the Company is referred to as “we,” “us,” and “our.”  Accessing the Site constitutes a use of the Site and an acceptance to our Privacy Policy.

Use of the Site, including all materials presented herein and all online Services provided by Company, is subject to the following Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy applies to all site visitors, customers and all other users of the Site.  By using the Site or Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy, without modification, and acknowledge reading it.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

The Site only collects the personal information you voluntarily provide to us, which includes your name and e-mail address, in order to subscribe to our newsletter, comment on our blog, and/or other personal information necessary to purchase Services and/or online products.

If you opt-in to receive our newsletter, the option to unsubscribe will be included in every e-mail. We do share your information with trusted third parties who provide support in running this Website including any blog or newsletter.  All parties will keep your information confidential and it will not be shared with unrelated third parties. We may record information relating to your use of the Site in order to help administer the Site and personalize your experience by improving customer service.

**ANTI-SPAM POLICY**

Your personal information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. You have the ability to unsubscribe from all e-mails and we have taken steps to ensure we compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.

**COOKIES**

We may send cookies, tracking pixels, and other related technologies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser, improve the quality of our service, and serve targeted advertising to you. The term “cookies” refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using your web browser settings. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all.  The Site may or may not respond to Do Not Track signals sent by your browser.

The Site may contain links to third party website.  Unless otherwise stated, this Privacy Policy only covers information that we collect from you on this Site. Any other link will be covered by the privacy policy of that specific site.  You acknowledge and accept that we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties.

**SECURITY**

We do our best to protect your information for any unauthorized access, misuse, or disclosure. For Customers purchasing the Company’s products, you acknowledge that the Company will have access to billing and other personal information. Such data may remain on Company’s database after termination of Agreement but will be deleted on a periodic basis. In addition, you acknowledge that the personal information you voluntarily share could be accessed or tampered with by a third party.  You agree that we are not responsible for any intercepted information shared through our Site without our knowledge or permission.  Additionally, you release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of such intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.  You agree to notify us for any breach of security or unauthorized use of your information.

**CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (COPPA) COMPLIANCE**

To access or use the Site, you must be 18 years old or older and have the requisite power and authority to enter into this Privacy Policy.  We do not knowingly collect or solicit data online from or market online to children under the age of 13.

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

You acknowledge and agree that you have reviewed this Site and this Privacy Policy and that you will continue to review this Policy to be aware of any modifications.  We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on this Website.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email: hello(at)splitly(dot)com.

Updated: 18th November 2016
